<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BeHear</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="socio">Economic</string>
    <string name="crime">Crime rate</string>
    <string name="edu">showData</string>
    <string name="votes">Politics</string>
    <string name="offlineMode">Explore</string>
    <string name="whats">What\'s That?</string>
    <string name="about">About Us</string>
    <string name="app_explanation">BeHear - Jerusalem like you\'ve never heard before!</string>
<string name="app_explanation2">Using BeHear, you can find out on real statistical data on the areas you are passing through, such as socio-econoic status and political votes, through engaging and informative sounds. </string>
    <string name = "app_explanation3"> Each parameter can be heard alone or in combination with the others, and the sounds will be played during your travel using location services. </string>
    <string name = "app_explanation4"> To hear the places without actually passing through them, choose "explore" and explore the map with your finger. </string>
        <string name= "app_explanation5"> Ready? Just start moving and BeHear.</string>
    <string name="app_explanation_choice">You can choose to hear these together, or each on alone.</string>
    <string name="develoment2"> BeHear was developed and implemented thanks to the conjoint effort of </string>
    <string name="develoment3"> Alon Bar, Tomer Behor, Inbar Tal and Tzeela Kirshenbaum</string>
    <string name="develoment4"> Under the supervision of Prof. Yair Bartal and Eran Erlich as a final work for the course \"On the Spectrum Between Science, Art and Technology\" (2016) </string>
    <string name="develoment5"> For suggestions and feedback: </string>
    <string name="develoment6"> behearapp@gmail.com </string>
    <string name="app_explanation_socio">by pressing here, BeHear will sonify the socio-economic status of different areas in jerusalem. This data is sonified through voices of babies: the more the area has a lower socio-economic status, the more the babies cry.</string>
    <string name="app_explanation_socio_from"> Data is taken from the Central Bureau of Statistics of Israel</string>
    <string name="app_explanation_votes"> By pressing here, BeHear will play the votes in the last elections of the different areas by speeches of politicians heading most elected party in this area.</string>
    <string name="app_explanation_votes_from">Data is taken from the Central Elections Committee. </string>
    <string name="app_explanation_explore">Choose \"explore\" in order to navigate in Jerusalem with your finger. This will enable you to place a marker on a chosen area of Jerusalem and hear the data you chose to hear. By Holding and dragging the marker you can hear the changes in the parameters of the area under your finger.</string>
</resources>
